Guide to the George Harrison Papers AIA.009
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
George Harrison Papers
1925-2003
1970-2000
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Harrison, George, 1915-2004
Durkan, Frank, 1930-2006
O'Dwyer & Bernstien
AIA.009
21.75 Linear Feet in 17 record cartons, 1 manuscript box, 2 oversize flat boxes, and 5 oversize folders.
George Harrison (1915-2004) was a socialist and revolutionary Irish Republican who spent his life supporting the causes of oppressed peoples around the globe. The collection consists of correspondence, legal files, memoranda, publications, ephemera, financial records, photographs, and material objects. The materials document his family history, Harrison's gunrunning trial, and political affiliations and involvements. This collection includes materials from many organizations in which Harrison was active during the period 1970-1995, especially the Irish American Defense Fund, the Irish Republican Socialist Committee of North America, the National Graves Association, and Republican Sinn Fein. The materials also reflect his interests in liberation movements in South Africa, Cuba, Latin America, Palestine and the Philippines, particularly through a collection of political buttons.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials open without restrictions.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Materials were donated in 1999 and 1997 by George Harrison, and in 2005 by Franck Durkel of O'Dwyer & Bernstien, executor of George Harrison's will.
Appraisal
In 2017, several t-shirts and a hat related to political rallies and campaigns were assessed as having minimal research value and were removed from the collection. These items had been included as part of a 1999 accretion added to the collection in 2017.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged in six series, each of which is arranged alphabetically by subject or title.
Personal, 1964-2001
Organizations and Memberships, 1925-2000
Pamphlets and Publications, 1937-2003
Oversize Materials: Publications and Fliers, 1963-1995
Photographs, 1982-1998
Ephemera, 1970-2000
Biographical Note
George Harrison (1915-2004) was a socialist and revolutionary Irish Republican who spent his life supporting the causes of oppressed peoples. Harrison was born in Shammer, Kilkelly, County Mayo, Ireland on May 2, 1915. As a youth he served in the East Mayo Brigade of the Irish Republican Army during the Irish Civil War (1922-1923). He immigrated to the United States in 1938 and served as an infantryman in the United States Army in the Pacific Theater of World War II. In 1948 Harrison began working as an armored car guard with Brinks, Inc. but was suspended in 1981 because of criminal charges filed against him.
Harrison was arrested on June 23, 1981 by the Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI) for violations of federal firearms laws. He, along with four others, was charged with running guns to the Provisional Irish Republican Army in the high-profile U.S. vs. Harrison, Falvey, Mullen, Gormley, and Flannery case argued in the Eastern District of New York Federal Court. Frank Durkan, also from County Mayo and a nephew of New York City lawyer and politician Paul O'Dwyer, represented Harrison, acknowledging that Harrison had shipped guns to Republicans in Ireland but arguing that American's Central Intelligence Agency (CIA) was complicit in the act. He was acquitted in 1982 and subsequently reinstated by Brinks with back pay in accordance with the order of a federal labor arbitrator (see folder Local 807 IBT vs. Brinks).
He retired from the company in the mid-1980s, but remained active in political causes, including opposition to racism and apartheid, as well as providing aid to Palestinians, Chileans, and other victims of poverty or injustices. Through his life, Harrison was active in many charitable endeavors, like providing funds to build a new parish church in his native town during the 1950s. He supported Irish American organizations that advocated the union of Northern Ireland with the Republic of Ireland, and came to the aid of Irish Republican prisoners held in the United States, Ireland, or Great Britain. He supported socialist political causes, but was also active in the New York City mayoral campaign of David Dinkins and the presidential campaigns of Jesse Jackson and Bill Clinton.
George Harrison died at his home in Park Slope, Brooklyn on October 6, 2004.
Custodial History
George Harrison contacted the Archives of Irish America in 1997 through Angela M. Carter, at that time proprietor of Irish Books and Graphics. Ten boxes of material were accessioned from Harrison's apartment in Park Slope, Brooklyn by Marion Casey in November 1997 and an additional eleven boxes of books and testimonials were donated by O'Dwyer & Bernstien in April 2005, acting as the executors of Harrison's estate. The accession number associated with this collection is 1997.069. Posters and framed memorabilia found in repository were added to this collection in 2015. The accession number associated with these materials is 2015.043. George Harrison sent an additional box of posters and memorabilia related to his involvement in human rights activism in 1999. The accession number associated with this gift is 2017.006.
Related Material at the Tamiment Library/Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Frank Durkan Papers AIA 008
Sean Prendiville Papers AIA 005
Jane Conlon Muller Oral History Collection AIA 012
Brian McGinn Papers AIA 015
Irish Republicanism Collection AIA 022
Sean Cronin Papers TAM 460
Printed Ephemera Collection of Organizational Files PE 036
Scope and Contents
The George Harrison Papers consist of correspondence, pamphlets, flyers, photographs, buttons, legal documents, memoranda, publications, research files, and material objects documenting Harrison's political activities and affiliations. The collection includes materials from numerous organizations in which Harrison was active during the 1970s through the mid-1990s, especially the Irish American Defense Fund, the Irish Republican Socialist Committee of North America, the National Graves Association, and Republican Sinn Fein. The materials, especially his collection of political buttons, also reflect his interest in liberation movements in South Africa, Cuba, Latin America, Palestine, and the Philippines. The papers also document Harrison's 1981-1982 defense against charges of gunrunning to the Provisional Irish Republican Army tried in the Eastern District of New York Federal Court case U.S. vs. Harrison, Falvey, Mullen, Gormley, and Flannery.
Separated Materials
Six boxes of books were removed from the manuscript collection to be cataloged as part of the Tamiment Library book collection. Issues of The Irish People, The Sovereign Nation, Irish Democrat, and Saoirse were separated to the Archives of Irish America Newspapers and Periodicals Collection (AIA 004)
Color photographs.; Pamphlets.; Human rights.; Hunger strikes -- Northern Ireland.; Irish Americans -- New York (State) -- New York -- Political activity.; Political campaigns -- New York (State) -- New York.; Anti-communist movements -- United States.; Fliers (printed matter); Political campaigns.; Human rights workers; Correspondence.; Trials (Political crimes and offenses) -- United States.; Black-and-white photographs.; Newsletters.; T-shirts.; Clippings (information artifacts); Buttons (information artifacts).; Political posters.; McAliskey, Bernadette Devlin, 1947-; International Brotherhood of Teamsters. Local 807 (New York, N.Y.); International Brotherhood of Teamsters; Veterans of the Abraham Lincoln Brigade; Irish Northern Aid Committee; Durkan, Frank, 1930-2006; Republican Sinn Féin; O'Dwyer, Paul, 1907-1998; Cox, Thomas J., 1906-; Clinton, Bill, 1946-; Sinn Fein; Irish Republican Army; O'Dwyer & Bernstien
- Series I. Personal, 1964-2001; 292862
  Scope and Content Note
  This series consists of correspondence, memoranda, legal documents, concerning Harrison's personal life, family history, and his defense against gunrunning charges in the U.S. vs. Harrison, Falvey, Mullen, Gormley, and Flannery case. Of note are speeches made by Harrison, a July 1983 application for a pistol permit, correspondence from Harrison's co-workers at Brinks, a book about the trial by Thomas Cox, and the October 1982 testimony of Bernadette Devlin McAliskey, a character witness at the trial.
  - Black and Tan Massacre, Mar 4, 1985; 293066 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Certificates, Honorariums, Awards and Recognitions, Tribute, 1964-1994, undated; 293095 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1960s-1970s; 293096 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence I, 1980s; 293097 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence II, 1980s; 293098 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1990-1992; 293099 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1993-1998; 293100 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, undated; 293101 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence A-C, May 1996, 1997; 293102 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence D-F, 1992-2001; 293103 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence: Family, 1964-1995; 293104 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence: Family, 1980-1995, undated; 293105 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence M-R, 1964-2001; 293106 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence: Snee, John, 1971-1982; 293107 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Greene, Michael - Ordination, Nov 10, 1979; 293108 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Invitations, 1984-1997; 293109 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Kennedy Memorial at Roscommon Park, circa 1984; 293110 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Local 807 International Brotherhood of Teamsters (Brinks), 1983-1984; 293111 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Memory Cards, 1960s-1990s; 293112 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Newspaper Clippings: Family and Personal History, circa 1982, 2000; 293113 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Newspaper Clippings/Articles: Ireland, North Ireland, undated; 293114 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - O'Dwyer, Paul: Political Campaigns, 1965, 1977; 293115 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Pistol Permit Application, Jul 1983; 293116 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Poetry, undated; 293117 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Protest Chants, undated; 293118 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Republican Sinn Fein (Sinn Fein Poblachtach), 1980-2000; 293119 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Republic Sinn Fein: Correspondence, 1990-1995; 293120 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Republican Sinn Fein: Correspondence - O'Connell, Daith, 1987-1990; 293121 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Republican Sinn Fein: Irish Freedom Movement (Sinn Fein Poblachtach), 1990; 293122 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Republican Sinn Fein: Republican Bulletin, 1986-1987; 293123 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Republican Sinn Fein: Victoria Branch (Australia), 1989-1990; 293124 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Sheey, John Joe: Funeral, 1980; 293125 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Speeches and Statements by Harrison, circa 1982, 1999, undated; 293126 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Speeches and Sponsorships by Harrison, 1982-1985; 293127 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Trial: Bail Release, Nov 19, 1982; 293128 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Trial: Briefing Note re: Noraid and Trial, Aug 4, 1983; 293129 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Trial: Correspondence, 1982; 293130 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Trial: Cox, Thomas - Statement and book "The Trial of the IRA Five" Riverside Books, 1992., 1982; 293131 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Trial: Freedom of Information Request, Mar 28, 1988; 293132 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Trial: Harrison-Falvey Defense Committee, 1982; 293133 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Trial: Harrison Statement on Arrest, Jun 19, 1981; 293134 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Trial: Judgment of Acquital, Nov 5, 1982; 293135 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Trial: Letters of Support, Jul 11, 1981; 293136 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Trial: Local 807 IBT v. Brinks Inc., 1982-1985; 293137 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Trial: Local 807 and Brinks Inc., 1983-1984; 293138 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Trial: McAliskey, Bernadette Devlin - Testimony, Oct 20, 1982; 293139 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Trial Newspaper Clippings, 1981-1983; 293140 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Trial: Search Warrant and Objects Seized, Jun 1981; 293141 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Tributes (Given by George Harrison), 1996-2001, undated; 293142 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Series II. Organizations and Memberships, 1925-2000; 292874
  Materials in this series include minutes, financial records, correspondence, and memoranda concerning a variety of domestic, Irish, and international political organizations Harrison belonged to, including Hands Off Cuba Coalition, the National Alliance Against Racist and Political Repression, and the Committee in Solidarity with Vietnam, Cambodia, and Laos. Although international in scope, much of the material documents Harrison's involvement with Irish and Irish American organizations, including his speech at a New York H-Block Armagh Committee rally; his work with the National Graves Association to provide memorials for Irish Republicans; his association with Republican Sinn Fein (also known as Sinn Fein Poblachtach), including letters from organizer Daithi O'Connell; his affiliation with the Irish American Defense Fund, which raised money during the 1980s for the legal defense of Irish Republican sympathizers facing criminal trial and deportation proceedings in American courts.
  - Ad Hoc Committee to Commemorate Sabra and Shatila, Sep 1983; 293146 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Ad Hoc Committee to Preserve Palestinian National Culture, 1986; 293147 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Ad Hoc Committee for a July Emergency Mobilization, Jun 1983, undated; 293148 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Ad Hoc Committee to Stop the Grand Jury/Resistant Task Force, 1984, undated; 293149 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Africa Fund, 1983-1997, undated; 293150 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Africa: General, 1983-1989; 293151 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - African National Congress (ANC), 1982-1987, undated; 293152 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - All Peoples Congress, 1982, 1984-1988, undated; 293153 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - American Connection, 1989; 293154 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Anti-Apartheid, 1982-1989; 293155 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Anti-Apartheid, 1990s; 293156 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Anti-Apartheid, undated; 293157 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Anti-Apartheid: Brooklyn Anti-Apartheid Coordinating Committee, 1986, undated; 293158 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Anti-Racism, Jan 1987, undated; 293159 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - April Actions for Peace, Jobs and Justice, 1985-1986; 293160 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Argentina, 1982, 1984, undated; 293161 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Casa De Las Americas, 1983-1995, undated; 293162 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Casa El Salvador, 1983-1987, undated; 293163 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Casa Nicaragua, 1983-1992, undated; 293164 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Center for Cuban Studies, 1985-1997, undated; 293165 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Donations: Acknowledgements, 1968, 1983-1998; 293166 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Central America and the Caribbean, 1983-1991, undated; 293167 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Chile, 1982-1990, undated; 293168 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Civilian Complaint Review Board in the City of New York, Sep 1992; 293169 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Clinton-Gore Campaigns, 1992-1996; 293170 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Coalition for a Free Central America, 1983; 293171 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Coalition for a Nuclear Free Harbor, 1985; 293172 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Columbia, 1984, undated; 293173 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Commission of Inquiry for the International War Crimes Tribunal, Jan 1992-Feb 1992; 293174 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Committee for Chilean Inquiry, 1983-1991, undated; 293186 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Committees of Correspondence: Corresponder, 1992-1999; 294444 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Committees of Correspondence - donation receipts, 1992-1996; 293187 (Box 3, Folder 2A)
  - Committees of Correspondence - Fliers and Meeting Notices, 1992-1996; 293188 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Committees of Correspondence: New York Mobilizer: Newsletter of the New York Committees of Correspondence, 1993-1994; 294445 (Box 3, Folder 3A)
  - Committee for David Dinkins, 1989, 1993-1994; 293189 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Committee for a Free Chile, 1983-1984, undated; 293190 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Committee for an Irish Forum, 1974; 293191 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Committee in Solidarity with the People of El Salvador (CISPES), 1984-1997; 293192 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Committee in Solidarity with the People of El Salvador (CISPES), undated; 293193 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Committee in Solidarity with Vietnam, Cambodia and Laos, 1990-1992; 293194 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Committee in Solidarity with Vietnam, Kampuchea and Laos, 1985-1990, undated; 293195 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Committee for a United Labor and People's May Day, 1984, 1989, undated; 293196 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Cuba Information Project, 1991-1997; 293197 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Cuba, 1986-1997, undated; 293198 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Daily News - Boycott the Daily News, undated; 293199 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Democratic Campaign Committee, 1992-1997, undated; 293200 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Donations (by Harrison), 1973-1994, 1997; 293201 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Eire Nua Building Fund, undated; 293202 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - El Salvador, 1983-1994, undated; 293203 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Free the Ohio 5, 1985, 1988; 293204 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Friends of Jim Brennan (Campaign), 1982-1994; 293205 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Frontline (Line of March Publication), 1984-1987, undated; 293206 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Grand Jury and Repression Position Papers (in Spanish), undated; 293207 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Grenada, 1983-1984, undated; 293208 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Guatemala, 1983-1990, undated; 293209 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Haiti, 1984-1993, undated; 293210 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Honduras, 1985-1986, undated; 293211 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Housing and Homelessness Causes, undated; 293212 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Interfaith Center on Corporate Responsibility/Immobilize Apartheid Coalition, 1987-1993, undated; 293213 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - International Peace for Cuba Appeal, 1991-1997; 293214 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Interreligious Foundation for Community Organization - U.S.-Cuba Friendship Committee, 1991-1997; 293215 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Interreligious Foundation for Community Organization: Pastors for Peace, 1990-1995, undated; 293216 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Iranian Student Association Organization of Iranian Peoples Fedaii Guerrillas, 1982, 1986, undated; 293217 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Ireland: Newspaper clippings and articles, 1950-1990, undated; 294419 (Box 3, Folder 32A)
  - Irish American Defense Fund, 1983-1984; 293218 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Irish American Defense Fund: Ancient Order of Hibernians, 1983; 293219 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Irish American Defense Fund: Burke, Maurice, Rev., 1983-1984; 293220 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Irish American Defense Fund: Correspondence/Donations, 1983; 293221 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Irish American Defense Fund: Financial Statements, 1983-1987; 293225 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Irish American Defense Fund: Fundraising Appeals and Brochures, 1984; 293222 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Irish American Defense Fund: Fundraising, Social Events, 1982-1986; 293223 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Irish American Defense Fund: Lists of Potential Donors, undated; 293224 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Irish American Defense Fund: Minutes and Agendas, 1983-Jun 1984; 293226 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Irish American Defense Fund: Minutes and Agendas, Jul 1984-1986; 293227 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Irish American Defense Fund: Minutes - Pledge Fund Committee, 1983; 293235 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Irish American Defense Fund: Organizational/Ad Campaigns, 1983; 293236 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Irish Brigade Association Newsletter: The Irish Volunteer, 2000; 294498 (Box 4, Folder 2A)
  - Irish Northern Aid Committee ( NORAID ), 1990, undated; 293237 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Irish Republican Army, 1956-1957; 293238 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Irish Republican Clubs - US and Canada, 1956-1978; 293239 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Irish Republican Socialist Party (Saorse), 1980; 293240 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Jesse Jackson Campaign, 1984, 1987-1992, undated; 293241 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Jewish Affairs, undated; 293242 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - John Brown Anti-Klan Committee, Mar 1985, undated; 293243 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Korea, 1983, undated; 293244 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Liam Cotter Memorial, undated; 293245 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Leonard Peltier Defense Committee (see also Series IV), 1985-1989; 293246 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Madre/Women's Peace Network Inc., 1985-1993, undated; 293247 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Nelson Mandela Reception Committee, 1990; 293248 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Marxist Studies, 1983, undated; 293249 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Mayo Foundation for the Handicapped (Paul O'Dwyer), 1967-1987; 293250 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Medical Aid for Central America - MEDICA, 1985-1990, undated; 293251 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - La Misa Campesina Nicaraguense: Program, Oct 21, 1984; 293252 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Middle East, 1979-1992; 293253 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Middle East, undated; 293254 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Militant Labor Forum, 1984-1987, undated; 293255 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Mission of Cuba to the United Nations, 1992-1996; 293256 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Na Fianna Eireann (Irish Republican Youth Movement), 1985-1986; 293257 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Na Fianna Eireann (Irish Republican Youth Movement), 1984; 293258 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - National Alliance Against Racist and Political Repression, 1989-1994; 293259 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - National Alliance Against Racist and Political Repression: Organizer, 1992-1993; 294457 (Box 4, Folder 25A)
  - National Association for Irish Justice, 1969, undated; 293260 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - National Campaign for Peace in the Middle East, 1990-1991, undated; 293261 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - National Central America Health Rights Network, 1987-1992, undated; 293262 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - National Committee to Free Puerto Rican Prisoners of War, 1984-1987, undated; 293263 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - National Committee for Independent Political Action, 1988-1989; 293264 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - National Graves Association, 1980-1990; 293265 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - National Graves Association: Correspondence of Sean Fitzpatrick, 1972-1986; 293266 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - National Graves Association: Correspondence of Joe and Mary Stagg, 1979; 293267 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - National Graves Association: Memorials, 1970-1980; 293268 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - National Hormel Strike Support Committee, 1986; 293269 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - National Labor Committee: Education Fund, Oct 1995; 293270 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - National Mobilization for Survival, May 19, 1987; 293271 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Native Americans, 1982-1991; 293272 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Rosemary Nelson Memorial Service, Apr 15, 1999; 293273 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - New Movement in Solidarity with Puerto Rican Independence and Socialism, 1987, 1989, undated; 293274 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - New York 8 and Defense Committee, 1984-1985; 293275 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - New York Anti-Apartheid Coordinating Council, 1985-1988, undated; 293276 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - New York H-Block Armagh Committee: General, 1980-1989; 293288 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - New York H-Block Armagh Committee Rally Harrison Speech, Dec 12, 1982; 293287 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - New York Labor Committee Against Apartheid, 1985-1991, undated; 293277 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - New York Socialist Workers Campaign, 1984-1986; 293286 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Nicaragua, 1983-1994, undated; 293289 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Nicaragua Construction Brigade, undated; 293290 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Nicaragua Solidarity Network, 1988-1991, undated; 293291 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Nicaragua Support Project, 1984, 1986, undated; 293292 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Nicaragua-United States Friendship Office, 1992-1994; 293293 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Northern Ireland, 1964, 1978, undated; 293294 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - November 29 Coalition: Correspondence and Clippings, 1982-1987, undated; 293295 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - November 29 Coalition: Fliers, undated; 293296 (Box 5, Folder 11)